Sanjali Das

Technical Content Writer

I have an experience of 7 years in creative writing, technical writing, copywriting, SEO, and digital marketing, delivering niche content to top firms based worldwide, for their company profile, website, mobile application, and more. As an undergraduate of mass communication, psychology, and law, as a content writer, I wish to conjure content that delivers the intended result, each time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Element8, Dubai

Content Developer

April 2020 - June 2023

- Collaborated closely with clients to develop content that best meets their needs and objectives
- Written content for website development, mobile application, E-commerce development, AI, Blockchain, and SaaS-based companies.
- Developed and managed content for multiple websites and blogs, ensuring accuracy and relevancy
- Wrote SEO-optimized content for web pages to improve web traffic and visibility
- Developed and implemented successful content marketing strategies to ensure maximum reach and engagement
- Ensured all content met industry standards and compliance regulations

Moonbox, Dubai

Copywriter

Jan 2018 - Mar 2020

- Collaborated with marketing, design, and content teams to create compelling copy for campaigns
- Wrote original copy for websites, brochures, emails, print ads, and other digital platforms
- Conducted research to develop an understanding of target audience and product offerings
- Proofread and edited copy to ensure accuracy and style

Nuox, India

Content Writer

Dec 2016 - Dec 2017

- Wrote, edited, and proofread copy for blog posts, website content, emails, press releases, white papers, and other marketing materials
- Written content for on-page as well as off-page content for websites.

CONTACT

304, Scheme 78 Part-2 Vijaynagar Indore, Madhya Pradesh, India, 452010 sanjalidas10@gmail.com +917489933151 https://www.linkedin.com/in/sanjalidas/

SKILLS

- Content Writing
- Copywriting
- Proofreading
- Editing
- •Time Management

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Mass Communication

Makhanlal Chaturvedi National University of Journalism and Communication, Bhopal

August 2020 - Present

Bachelor in Psychology

Indira Gandhi National University, Delhi

November 2019 - March 2023

Certifications

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing by Google

SEO Analytics by Google

Basic AI from Deep Learning.AI